甚至那位将螺旋弹簧玩具 取名为Slinky的人。
even the person who came up with the name on the Slinky.
只有一个问题。
There's just one problem.
只有一小部分的讣文
Only a small percentage of them
在记录女性和有色人种的人生。
chronicle the lives of women and people of color.
出于这个动机，我创立了一个项目，
That's the impetus behind a project I created
叫做“被忽略者”，
called "Overlooked,"
目的是帮被边缘化的族群说故事，
which tells the stories of marginalized groups of people
他们从来没有讣文。
who never got an obit.
这是个机会，能让报社 重温它168年的历史，
It's a chance for the newspaper to revisit its 168-year existence
去填补那些不论
and fill in the gaps
因为什么理由而被排除的人的鸿沟。
for people who were, for whatever reason, left out.
这是个可以修正过去错误的机会，
It's a chance to right the wrongs of the past,